Finding aid for Mike Wallace CBS/60 Minutes Papers, 1922-2007
Bentley Historical Library
- General Files
  - 1979
    - Topical
      - Law Enforcement Intelligence Unit (LEIU) (Box 79)
      - Leighton, Dan (payment for services) (Box 79)
      - Liddy, G. Gordon (Box 79)
      - Lewis, Vivian (free-lance) (Box 79)
      - Lowery, Dr. Joseph (Southern Christian Leadership Conference) (Box 79)
      - Malcolm X (Box 79)
      - Mankiewicz, Frank (National Public Radio) (Box 79)
      - McKenna, Siobhan (Box 79)
      - Mengele, Dr. Josef (Box 79)
      - Mineral Rights (Box 79)
      - Mother Jones Magazine (Box 79)
      - Nuclear Power (sabotage at Virginia's Surry Plant) (Box 79)
      - Onassis, Jacqueline (Box 79)
      - Palm Springs (Box 79)
      - Phony Degrees (Box 79)
      - The Pope (Box 79)
      - Porcello, Michael and Florence (disabled son Dominic and efforts to get assistance) (Box 79)
      - Posner, Victor (Box 79)
      - Rubin, Dr. Edward (Box 79)
      - Russia (Box 79)
      - Saudi Arabia (Box 79)
      - Siegel, Judy (Jerusalem Post reporter) (Box 79)
      - Sirica, John (Box 79)
      - Soldier of Fortune Magazine (Box 79)
      - Straight, Michael (book jacket blurb) (Box 79)
      - Sugar Marketing (Box 79)
      - Swedish Prisons (Box 79)
      - Syrian Jews (updates) (Box 79)
      - Transsexuals (Box 79)
      - Turkish Prisons (Americans) (Box 79)
      - Venezuela (Box 79)
      - Welfare Fraud Hotline (Box 79)
      - The West Bank (Box 79)
      - Wisconsin State Attorney General (chain letter) (Box 79)
      - Zenker, Arnold (television consultant) (Box 79)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Broadcasts other than 60 Minutes (Box 79)
      - Inside Yesterday"Target USA,", August 21, 1979 (Box 79)
      - "Iran, the Desperate Dilemma," narrated by Mike Wallace (Box 79)
      - Mike Wallace At Large (Box 79)
  - 1980
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 79)
      - Expense Reports, 3 folders (Box 79)
      - Travel (Box 79)
    - Correspondence
      - Assistant's, 1980-1981 (Box 79)
      - General (Box 79)
      - Personal A-Z, 6 folders (Box 80)
      - Press Related (Box 80)
      - Story Related (Box 80)
      - Viewer Mail (Box 80)
    - * Personal
      - "Biography" Series Proposal (Box 80)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 80)
      - Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation (Box 80)
      - PBS Interview by John Calloway (Box 80)
      - Resumes (Box 80)
      - Speeches and Appearances, 16 folders
        - Speeches, general (Box 80)
        - American Society of Travel Agents, January 12 (Minneapolis, MN) (Box 80)
        - National Retail Merchants Association, January 15 (New York, NY) (Box 80)
        - American Association of School Administrators, February 16 (Anaheim, CA) (Box 80)
        - Alfred I. duPont-Columbia University Awards, February 28 (New York, NY) (Box 80)
        - Temple Emanu-El, March 26 (Miami Beach, FL) (Box 80)
        - The Fund for Free Expression, Symposium on the Frank Snepp Case, April 2 (New York, NY) (Box 80)
        - Centennial Celebration of the University of Michigan Economics Department, April 12 (Ann Arbor, MI) (Box 80)
        - Constitutional Rights Foundation Annual Spring Law Day Dinner, April 27 (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 80)
        - Association of Western Hospitals, April 28 (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 80)
        - Friars Annual Testimonial Dinner honoring Henry Kissinger, May 3 (New York, NY) (Box 80)
        - Hall of Fame, Bentley College, May 20-21, circa 1980 (Box 80)
        - Bank Administration Institute, September 24 (Detroit, MI) (Box 80)
        - National Sporting Goods Association, September 28 (New York, NY) (Box 80)
        - Power Transmission Distributors Association, October 13 (Houston, TX) (Box 80)
        - Brandeis University National Board of Fellows Conference and Award, October 18 (Washington, DC) (Box 80)
      - Wallace Fiction Prize, 1980-1981 (Box 80)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Mike Wallace At Large (Box 80)
  - 1981
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 80)
      - Expenses, 3 folders (Box 80)
      - Telephone Register, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 3 folders (Box 81)
      - Personal, 6 folders (Box 81)
      - Press Related (Box 81)
    - Personal
      - * Commencement Speeches--Texts (Box 81)
      - Killed Story on Haiti--controversy (Box W2)
      - * Miscellaneous (Box 81)
      - * Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation (Box 81)
      - Speeches and Appearances, 10 folders
        - Southeastern Poultry and Egg Association, January 21 (Atlanta, GA) (Box 81)
        - Ball State University, February 10 (Muncie, IN) (Box 81)
        - International Tape/Disc Association, March 18 (Hollywood, FL) (Box 81)
        - National School Board, April 14 (Dallas, TX) (Box 81)
        - Millbrook School Tamarack Dinner, April 23 (Millbrook, NY) (Box 81)
        - American Hardware Supply Company, May 3 (Harrisburg, PA) (Box 81)
        - University of Pennsylvania, May 15 (Philadelphia, PA) (Box 81)
        - Mercy College Commencement, May 17 (Westchester, NY) (Box 81)
        - Providence College Commencement, May 18 (Providence, RI) (Box 81)
        - University of Hartford Summer Seminar, June 18 (West Hartford, CT) (Box 81)
        - Media and Society Seminar (Columbia University), October 10 (Box 81)
        - Yankelovich, Skelly and White, Inc. talk, November 19, 1981 (Box 81)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Mike Wallace At Large (Box 81)
  - 1982
    - Administrative
      - Expense Reports, 4 folders (Box 81)
      - Press Coverage (Box 81)
      - Purchase Requisitions (Box 81)
      - Research Services (Box 81)
      - Telephone Register, 3 folders (Box 81)
    - Correspondence
      - Assistant's, 3 folders (Box 81)
      - General (Box 81)
      - Personal A-Z, 6 folders (Box 82)
      - Press Related (Box 82)
      - Stories Pending (Box 82)
      - Story Related (Box 82)
    - * Personal
      - Resumes (Box 82)
      - Speeches and Appearances, 7 folders
        - John Jay College, February 22 (New York, NY) (Box 82)
        - Ralph Nader's Second Annual Student Conference on Investigative Reporting, March 21 (canceled, Washington, DC) (Box 82)
        - Louisiana Bankers Association, April 3 (New Orleans, LA) (Box 82)
        - Impact Newsletter, April 6 (New York, NY) (Box 82)
        - DeAnza College, April 13 (canceled, Cupertino, CA) (Box 82)
        - The New School for Social Research, October 28 (New York, NY) (Box 82)
        - Volunteer Trustees of Not-for-Profit Hospitals, November 8 (Palm Beach, FL) (Box 82)
      - Walker, Harry, 1980-1982 (Box 82)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Mike Wallace At Large (Box 82)
  - 1983
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 82)
      - Expense Reports, 5 folders (Box 82)
      - Expense Reports Adjustments (Box 82)
      - General Legal (Box 82)
      - Press clippings (Box 82)
      - Purchase Requisitions (Box 82)
      - Syria visa applications (Box 82)
      - Telephone Register (Box 82)
      - Working Press Card Application (Box 82)
    - Correspondence
      - Assistant's (Box 82)
      - Department of Defense (Box 83)
      - Internal (Box 83)
      - Personal, 5 folders (Box 83)
      - Press Related (Box 83)
      - Stories Pending (Box 83)
      - Story Related (Box 83)
      - Telexes Received (Box 83)
      - Telexes Sent (Box 83)
    - * Personal
      - Auction Donations (visit Mike Wallace/tour studio), 1982-1983 (Box 83)
      - Center for Investigative Reporting, Introduction to Dan Noyes and David Weir Raising Hell (1983) (Box 83)
      - Invitations Accepted (Box 83)
      - Invitations Declined (Box 83)
      - Livingston Awards for Young Journalists (Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation) (Box 83)
      - Resumes (Box 83)
      - Speeches and Appearances, 9 folders
        - Georgia Association of Broadcasters, January 18 (Macon, GA) (Box 83)
        - Young Lawyers' Association Panel Discussion, February 24 (New York, NY) (Box 83)
        - PBS "Why in the World," March 7 (New York, NY) (Box 83)
        - New York Press Association, March 19 (Albany, NY) (Box 83)
        - Intrepid Aircraft Carrier/Sea-Air-Space Museum, April 13 (New York, NY) (Box 83)
        - Wine and Spirits Wholesalers of America, May 25 (Atlanta, GA) (Box 83)
        - Amway Corporation Event and "Larry King Live" Appearance, October 12 (Grand Rapids, MI) (Box 83)
        - Better Government Association, October 24 (Chicago, IL?) (Box 83)
        - CBS Year Award Dinner, November 3 (New York, NY), 1920/1930 (Box 83)
  - 1984
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 83)
      - CBS Memos--Video Cassette Gifts (Box 83)
      - Dead Story Files to Storage (Box 83)
      - Expense Reports, 4 folders (Box 83)
      - Expense Reports Adjustments (Box 83)
      - General Legal (Box 83)
      - Passport information (Box 83)
      - Press Coverage (Box 83)
      - Purchase Requisitions (Box 83)
      - Telephone Register (Box 83)
      - Travel (Box 84)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 5 folders (Box 84)
      - Assistant's (Box 84)
      - Center for Investigative Reporting (Box 84)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 84)
      - Press Related (Box 84)
      - Stories Pending (Box 84)
      - Story Related (Box 84)
      - Syria Responses (Box 84)
      - Telexes Received (Box 84)
      - Telexes Sent (Box 84)
    - * Personal
      - Auction Donation (visit Mike Wallace/tour studio) (Box 84)
      - "Biography" Series Proposal (Box 84)
      - Christmas List (Box 84)
      - Emmy Award Application (Box 84)
      - Invitations Accepted (Box 84)
      - Invitations Declined (Box 84)
      - Jury Deferment (Box 84)
      - Livingston Awards for Young Journalists (Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation) (Box 84)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 84)
      - Resumes (Box 84)
      - Speech--Text (Box 84)
      - Speeches and Appearances, 8 folders
        - Sundome Center for the Performing Arts, March 12 (Sun City, AZ) (Box 84)
        - Skip Blumberg Interview, March 29 (Box 85)
        - Gordon Stewart, April 2 (New York, NY) (Box 85)
        - Albright College, April 6 (Reading, PA) (Box 85)
        - Washington Hebrew Congregation, April 12 (Washington, DC) (Box 85)
        - Overseas Press Club, April 25 (New York, NY) (Box 85)
        - "Men and Women: The Big Thaw," Ms. and Esquire Forum, May 9 (New York, NY) (Box 85)
        - Libel Defense Resource Center Annual Dinner, November 7 (New York, NY) (Box 85)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Newsnotes and Comment, CBS News (Box 85)
  - 1985
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 85)
      - Expense Reports, 4 folders (Box 85)
      - Expense Reports Adjustments (Box 85)
      - General Legal (Box 85)
      - Press Coverage (Box 85)
      - Purchase Requisitions (Box 85)
      - Telephone Register (Box 85)
      - Travel (Box 85)
      - Working Press Card Application (Box 85)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 6 folders (Box 85)
      - Assistant's (Box 85)
      - Hospital (Box 86)
      - Letter Samples, 1975-1985 (Box 86)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 86)
      - Personal (Box 86)
      - Stories Pending (Box 86)
      - Telexes Sent and Received (Box 86)
    - * Personal
      - American Lawyer Magazine, response to hypothetical case (Box 86)
      - Auction Donations (visit Mike Wallace/tour studio) (Box 86)
      - Bentley Historical Library 1984, 2001 Donation, 1982-1990, 2001, 1982-2001 (Box 86)
      - Invitations Accepted (Box 86)
      - Invitations Declined (Box 86)
      - Journalists in Residence (fundraising letter), University of Michigan, 1985-1986 (Box 86)
      - Livingston Awards (Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation) (Box 86)
      - Medal of Liberty Selection Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 86)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 86)
      - Museum of Communications (Chicago, IL), 1983 (Box 86)
      - Press Speech (Box 86)
      - Resumes (Box 86)
      - Speeches and Appearances (arranged chronologically)
        - Television Academy Hall of Fame, March 25 (Santa Monica, CA) (Box 86)
        - American Society of Newspaper Editors Convention, April 12 (Washington, DC) (Box 86)
        - The Kirchman Company, April 13 (Lake Buena Vista, FL) (Box 86)
        - Promenade Lecture Series, New College/University of South Florida, April 14 (Sarasota, FL) (Box 86)
        - Holocaust Memorial Council's Evening of Commemoration, April 21 (Washington, DC?) (Box 86)
        - Harvard Law Forum, April 25 (Cambridge, MA) (Box 86)
        - The Christophers Dinner, May 8 (canceled, New York, NY) (Box 86)
        - Dialogue Forum, May 22 (canceled, Washington, DC) (Box 86)
        - Mabel Mercer Foundation, June 9 (canceled, New York, NY, includes cassette tape) (Box 86)
        - North American Watch Company, July 29 (New York, NY) (Box 86)
        - University Speakers International, October 21 (Toronto, Canada) (Box 86)
        - CBS Law Department, October 27 (New York, NY) (Box 86)
        - Israel Bonds, November 3 (Denver, CO) (Box 86)
        - Interfaith Hunger Appeal, November 20 (New York, NY) (Box 86)
        - Town Hall Series of Cleveland (Cleveland, OH), January 29, 1986 (Box 86)
    - Topical
      - Ideas-Lowell Bergman (Box 86)
      - Ideas-David and Julie Eisenhower (Box 86)
      - Ideas-Marion Goldin (Box 86)
      - Ideas-Barry Lando (Box 86)
      - Ideas-Chuck Lewis (Box 86)
      - Ideas-Mercenary medicine in Arizona (Box 86)
      - Ideas-Miscellaneous (Box 86)
  - 1986
    - Administrative
      - Air Travel Mileage Records (Box 87)
      - CBS Memos (Box 87)
      - Expenses, 5 folders (Box 87)
      - Jury Duty, 1985-1986 (Box 87)
      - Passport and Visa Information
        - Afghanistan (Box 87)
        - China (Box 87)
        - South Africa (Box 87)
        - Thailand (Box 87)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 6 folders (Box 87)
      - Assistant's, 3 folders (Box 87)
      - Gary Korkala (Box 87)
      - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 87)
      - Personal (Box 87)
      - Press Related (Box 87)
    - * Personal
      - Accuracy in Media Newsletters, 1980-1986 (Box 87)
      - Thomas Hart Benton Exhibition, Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art (Kansas City, MO) (Box 87)
      - Charles Collingwood Memorial Scholarship, George Heller Foundation, American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) Memorial Foundation (New York, NY) (Box 87)
      - Ron Dworkin Documentation (regarding dishonesty charges related to General Westmoreland's infiltration story) (Box 87)
      - Emmy Award Application (Box 87)
      - Expenses (Box 87)
      - Invitations Accepted (Box 88)
      - Invitations Declined (Box 88)
      - Livingston Awards for Young Journalists, Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation (Box 88)
      - Museum of Broadcast Communications (Chicago, IL) (Box 88)
      - Resumes (Box 88)
      - Liz Smith Woman's Roast, February 11 (Box 88)
      - Speeches and Appearances
        - "The Future of American Business," New York University, March 7 (New York, NY) (Box 88)
        - Town Hall of Naples, Florida, March 23 (Box 88)
        - CBS Morning News Interview, September 17 (Box 88)
        - "Humor and the Presidency" Symposium, Gerald R. Ford Foundation, September 18 and 19 (Grand Rapids, MI) (Box 88)
        - Arthur Miller Oral History Interview, John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, November 30 (Washington, DC) (Box 88)
      - Wallace Fiction Prize, Yale University (Box 88)
    - Topical
      - Ideas-Miscellaneous (Box 88)
      - Ideas-Nuclear Winter (Box 88)
      - Ideas-Syria-Iran (Box 88)
      - Ideas-Westway Highway Project (Box 88)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Newsnotes and Comment, CBS News (Box 88)
      - 60 Minutes Bluesheets (brief story topics), 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - 1987
    - Administrative
      - Blue sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 88)
      - CBS Memos (Box 88)
      - Chartered Jet Services (Box 88)
      - El Salvador trip file (Box 88)
      - Expenses (Box 88)
      - Frequent Flyer Documentation (Box 88)
      - Passport and Visa Information (Box 88)
      - Telephone Registers (Box 88)
      - Working Press (Box 88)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 7 folders (Box 88)
      - Accuracy in Media, Inc., 1982-1987 (Box 88)
      - Assistant's, 3 folders (Box 89)
      - China (Box 89)
      - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 89)
      - Proposals (Box 89)
    - * Personal
      - "Biography" Series (Box 89)
      - Boys' Club (Box 89)
      - Center for Investigative Reporting (Box 89)
      - Century Association Nomination (Box 89)
      - Charles Collingwood Memorial Scholarship, George Heller Foundation, American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) Memorial Foundation (New York, NY) (Box 89)
      - Emmy Award Nominations (Box 89)
      - Interlochen Celebration Committee, (Interlochen, MI) (Box 89)
      - Invitations Accepted (Box 89)
      - Invitations Declined (Box 89)
      - Livingston Awards for Young Journalists, Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation (Box 89)
      - Mike Wallace Fellowship in Investigative Reporting, University of Michigan (Box 89)
      - Museum of Broadcast Communications (Chicago, IL) (Box 89)
      - Museum of Broadcasting (New York, NY) (Box 89)
      - Obituaries (Box 89)
      - Party List (Box 89)
      - Press Coverage, General (Box 89)
      - Resumes (Box 89)
      - 60 Minutes Twentieth Anniversary Party, Guest List (Box 89)
      - Speeches and Appearances
        - Milton Gordon Tribute (Box 89)
        - Touche Ross and Co., January 29 (New York, NY) (Box 89)
        - David Susskind Memorial, March (Box 89)
        - Florida International University, March 6 (Miami, FL) (Box 89)
        - Kirk Douglas, April 6 (American Academy of Dramatic Arts, New York, NY) (Box 89)
        - Touche Ross, April 28 (Los Angeles, CA) (Box 89)
        - Commencement Address and Trip File, University of Michigan, May 2 (Ann Arbor, MI), 2 folders (Box 89)
        - Boston Fidelity Investment Speech, May 7 (Boston, MA) (Box 89)
        - American Association on Mental Deficiency, May 27 (Box 89)
        - William Styron Tribute, August 29 (Martha's Vineyard, MA) (Box 89)
        - Illinois Broadcasters Association, October 9 (Chicago, IL (Box 89)
        - Bankers Trust Company, October 10 (canceled, Charleston, SC) (Box 89)
        - "Ethics in America: Columbia University Seminars on Media and Society, November 1 (Boston, MA) (Box 89)
        - Yale Daily News, November 20 (New Haven, CT) (Box 89)
        - "Interviews with Interviewers," New York Public Library, November 24 (Box 89)
        - Foundation for Children with Learning Disabilities Awards Dinner, December 5 (New York, NY) (Box 89)
      - Wallace Fiction Prize, Yale University (Box 89)
    - Topical
      - Ideas--Miscellaneous (Box 89)
      - Iran-Gate (Box 89)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - Newsnotes and Comment, CBS News (Box 89)
      - A Presidential Portrait, CBS News (Box 89)
  - 1988
    - Administrative
      - Bonus Mileage (Box 90)
      - CBS Information and Records Management, 1986-1988 (Box 90)
      - CBS Memos (Box 90)
      - Expense Accounts, 4 folders (Box 90)
      - Legal, General (Box 90)
      - London, Germany, and Georgia Trip Expenses and Itinerary (Box 90)
      - Manhattan Limousine Invoices and Receipts (Box 90)
      - Passport/visa information (Box 90)
      - Skyline Credit Ride Limousine Invoices and Receipts (Box 90)
      - Telephone Registers (Box 90)
      - Visa Application, Poland (Box 90)
      - Working Press Card Application (Box W2)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 7 folders (Box 90)
      - Assistant's, 3 folders (Box 90)
      - China (Box 90)
      - Marty Eisenstein regarding finances (Box 90)
      - Marion Goldin (Box 90)
      - Personal-Received (Box 90)
      - Personal-Sent (Box 90)
      - Proposals (Box 90)
    - * Personal
      - Boys' Club (Box 90)
      - Center for Communications, New York, NY (Box 90)
      - Charles Collingwood Fund, George Heller Memorial Scholarship, American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) Memorial Foundation, New York, NY (Box 90)
      - Richard Clurman's The Media's Years of Reckoning, response (Box 90)
      - Emmy Award Nomination (Box 90)
      - Enrichment Fund, College of Literature, Science, and the Arts, University of Michigan (Box 90)
      - Finances (Box 90)
      - Golden Scroll Award, The Jewish Advocate (Box 90)
      - "The Hate That Hate Produced," (Malcolm X interview for documentary series Eyes on the Prize) (Box 90)
      - Interlochen Celebration Committee, (Interlochen, MI) (Box 90)
      - Invitations Declined (Box 90)
      - Joint Chiefs of Staff War Game, Pensacola, FL (Box 90)
      - Jury Duty (Box 90)
      - Mike Wallace Fellowship in Investigative Reporting, University of Michigan (Box 90)
      - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 90)
      - Moscow Trip with Ira Rosen, September 7-10 (Box 91)
      - Museum of Broadcast Communications, Chicago, IL (Box 91)
      - Museum of Broadcasting, New York, NY (Box 91)
      - Obituaries (Box 91)
      - Paris Facilities, CBS (Box 91)
      - Press Coverage, General (Box 91)
      - Nancy Reagan (Box 91)
      - Resumes (Box 91)
      - Speeches and Appearances
        - Contracts and Waivers (Box 91)
        - General (including cassette and reel-to-reel for unidentified August 4 speech) (Box 91)
        - Werner Erhard and Associates, March 19 (San Francisco, CA) (Box 91)
        - Touche Ross, March 29 (Springfield, NJ) (Box 91)
        - Touche Ross, April 11 (Chicago, IL) (Box 91)
        - Marketing Conference of the Systems Integration Division, IBM, April 14 (Marco Island, FL) (Box 91)
        - Long Island Board of Realtors (Harry Walker Speech), April 19 (Great Neck, NY) (Box 91)
        - "Ethics in Broadcast Journalism" Panel, Center for Communications, April 21 (New York, NY) (Box 91)
        - Searle and Company (Harry Walker Speech regarding malpractice), May 1 (Boston, MA) (Box 91)
        - Focus on Long Island Operations (FOLIO) Awards Luncheon, Long Island Coalition for Fair Broadcasting, May 13 (Long Island, NY) (Box 91)
        - "Wisemen" Dinner, Johnson & Johnson, May 18 (Box 91)
        - Mitchell Hutchins Asset Management, August 29 (New York, NY) (Box 91)
        - Southern Methodist University, September 8 (Dallas, TX) (Box 91)
        - Jones Stores (for Men's Forum, Harry Walker Speech), October 25 (Kansas City, MO) (Box 91)
        - Walter Cronkite Tribute, December 5 (New York, NY) (Box 91)
        - Cotter and Company (True Value) National Sales Luncheon, December 6 (Chicago, IL) (Box 91)
      - Wallace Fiction Prize, Yale University (Box 91)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - CBS Evening News, January 11-15 (Box 91)
      - Newsnotes and Comment, CBS News (Box 91)
      - 60 Minutes Bluesheets (brief story topics), 1987-1988; 3 folders (Box 91)
  - 1989
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 91)
      - Expense Accounts (none for October through December), 3 folders (Box 91)
      - Frequent Flyer Information (Box 91)
      - Telephone Registers (Box 91)
      - Visa-Soviet Union (Box 91)
    - Correspondence
      - A-D (Box 91)
      - E-W (no X through Z correspondence), 5 folders (Box 92)
      - Assistant's, 3 folders (Box 92)
      - Ethel Goldstein--Sent (financial) (Box 92)
      - Personal--Received (Box 92)
      - Personal--Sent (Box 92)
    - * Personal
      - Boys Club (Box 92)
      - Emmy Award Nominations, 1987-1989 (Box 92)
      - Enrichment Fund, College of Literature, Science, and the Arts, University of Michigan (Box 92)
      - Interlochen Center for the Arts (Box 92)
      - Livingston Awards for Young Journalists, Mollie Parnis Livingston Foundation (Box 92)
      - Nathan Mayhew Seminars of Martha's Vineyard, Inc. (Box 92)
      - Martha's Vineyard (Box 92)
      - Mike Wallace Fellowship in Investigative Reporting, University of Michigan (Box 92)
      - Nancy Reagan House, Phoenix Center (Box 92)